{
    "subject": "resource/Manhattan_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/Woody_Allen",
    "human_readable": "Woody Allen wrote Manhattan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7960322499275208,
            "question": "What kind of work did Woody Allen create titled Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6739320158958435,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie written by Woody Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6726115345954895,
            "question": "What are some critical reviews of Woody Allen's Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6126601099967957,
            "question": "Who wrote the movie Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44005516171455383,
            "question": "Has Woody Allen won any awards for his work on Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27964097261428833,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Woody Allen's films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13338401913642883,
            "question": "In what year was the film Manhattan released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11635467410087585,
            "question": "What is known about the plot of the movie Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10026895254850388,
            "question": "Is Manhattan a book, a play, or a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09737103432416916,
            "question": "What is the setting of the movie Manhattan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Woody Allen wrote Manhattan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8827_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Manhattan a book, a play, or a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8827_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about the plot of the movie Manhattan?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8827_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was the film Manhattan released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8827_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8827_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{\"output\": \"yes\"}`\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Woody Allen directed and wrote many films, including Manhattan. For example, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8827/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt states \"Manhattan can be said to be Woody Allen\u2019s playground.  He has directed and written countless films that have been filmed here in wonderful New York.\" This suggests that Woody Allen was the author of Manhattan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Woody Allen directed and wrote the film \"Manhattan,\" supporting the statement that Woody Allen wrote Manhattan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}